coucou les amis (French greeting)
Hello everyone, my cuties,
I am your Yooupi,
welcome to my channel
. Now I am still in Masirah Island, Oman.
Today I will try to
catch a huge fish in Masirah Island. The moray eel
is called the naked-breasted eel.
I am quite confident in myself.
Let ’s go.
Masirah Island is about 95 kilometers from north to south.
It takes an hour to drive
. The place we are going to today
can be reached by car in about half an hour.
I have now arrived at the beach. It's
really beautiful.
It's 2:00 in the afternoon and
the temperature has reached 27 or 8 degrees. It's
quite hot,
but the temperature of the sea water is very comfortable.
It's very refreshing to catch the sea
in this place. I just picked up a piece of wood on the ground there. The stick
is just right to use as my fishing rod. It
is very strong
and not weathered.
It is ready for use.
The tide has not completely gone down yet.
I need to wait for another hour or so.
The seaside environment looks
like it is in stock.
There are all oysters down there.
Look at this. The puddles
are full of sea urchins. They are
so beautiful. Are these
sea urchins edible?
I want to pick them up
and taste them. I want
to
see
if
they are beautiful. The spines are still moving.
Crack them open and taste them. Try
the sea urchins from Oman.
It's a bit like the long thorn sea urchin. The spines
are so long
and don't look very fat
on the inside
. Moreover, the freshness of
yellow gall is a bit worse
, not particularly fresh,
but it is edible.
Let's make the fishing rod first
, hang it on the hook with a fishing line
and find a wooden stick. Once the winding
is done and strong,
let’s first try to use the conch meat we picked up to catch
. The local fishermen told me that
this kind of bare-breasted eel
will live in this kind of puddle after low tide.
Let’s find
another
pit and continue.
There was a colorful fish
right next to this rock.
It was so beautiful
. Did you see
an eel
in the hole
? It tore off a piece of snail
meat . It was so strong and so
angry
that I will fight you to the end today. Oh
my god.
Let's continue trying.
Photographer: Two of
them
were torn off again.
I put the meat too far inside and
once it was pulled into the stone, I couldn't get it out.
It got stuck in the crack of the stone
. Come again, come again.
Look, it can't be lured out
. This thing is quite smart.
Why is the other one missing?
Photographer: After
I fished for 10 minutes,
I felt that the eels were tired of
eating this thing.
Is it easier to find other
fish, crabs, etc. to
catch you ?
If it has an S angle,
you can't run away.
This fish is quite big.
It's bigger than the miscellaneous
fish I caught. I divided the fish into three parts
and hung it up to try
. I don't know
if it eats it. I tried it again and
it ate me. A lot of fish came
out and it came out
so big. It retracted
again
. It retracted and
bit.
I felt it was so fat. It
was like something was slipping
around
. I ate it this time. I waited for it to eat for a while and it got
stuck in its esophagus. Then I tried again. Pull
it, hook it,
hook it, hook it,
don’t unhook, don’t unhook,
look at this mouth, I’m scared to look at it.
Lighten, light,
light, light,
struggle
. You’re still struggling.
I ’ll
pull you up.
I ’ll strangle you
. Oh, la, la
, I’ll strangle you. Oh my God,
what are you doing
? You've strangled yourself.
This is like walking a dog. Oh
my god, someone
else is walking a dog. I
'm walking an eel here.
Oh my god. Oh my god. It's so sunny. I fished for that one
. It made me sweat all over
and took off my sun protection clothes.
There is another one inside. I
want to fight it till the end. Today
I fucked up its brother.
It has become alert.
After eating,
it slowly
comes out and comes out.
You can see that
all the sand inside has been dug out by it.
Slowly. Slowly,
I have already experienced
the decoupling.
Did you not
take it off? Slowly,
I hooked its mouth. Did you see its mouth?
Come out . I hope it does
n’t get decoupled.
Just look at
its mouth.
I hooked one of the tips of its mouth. I
hope it doesn’t get decoupled.
This one is not as big as the one just now,
but it's pretty big.
This is the bare-breasted eel
. It really looks like a large eel.
Its mouth looks like a poisonous snake.
I can tell you that
there are fish in those stone crevices. Are you
addicted to fishing
? That fish is so powerful
and you feel so good when you catch it.
Come on, my friend,
you have been hooked by me.
This is actually the same as walking a fish.
I have figured out the way now.
You can't pull it hard.
Just pull it. Don't come out.
Look
, this big one
is as long as my legs
. It started to roll again and
entangled itself.
What kind of spinning top is this?
Oh my God,
I caught three
big ones.
Photographer: I watched OK Brother fight that day. The ones that are thicker than thighs.
Contact my old friend OK brother
right away and take me to catch the ones that are thicker than thighs.
Since I have to go to OK brother tomorrow to catch the big
ones, I will let them go. Let’s
all go. Let’s go.
Look at that one. I
lost all my energy very quickly , but
it recovered after a while.
Hello Yooupi
, I finally got my OK brother.
Sorry, I was too busy yesterday and didn’t accompany you
. You have to get me a
big conger eel today. Come up to
that sea. The eel is as thick as my thigh.
Have you ever
caught a big one before
? OK, OK. Just finish
it and walk away.
Yooupi, your clothes are too thick
. You see, I am only 1.8 mm and you are already 5 mm.
My diving suit 5 Millimeters thick
because
the water temperature in the North Atlantic Ocean in France is usually cold,
but the water temperature in Marsila Island is
more than 20 degrees. I
took a weighted lead block.
The naked-breasted eel is usually about 6-7 meters underwater
. I brought a lead block today. We can’t use an S
buckle on a three kilogram
lead weight.
If you encounter any danger underwater,
just pull it open and it will open.
You guys have reached this point
and it doesn’t make sense if you don’t like it and follow it.
Bring two spearguns. Do you want the long one or the short one?
The
short one doesn't seem to be very sharp,
but it should be fine.
Yooupi, your dress is too thick.
Use this thin one.
I'll change it to this one. It's a bit thick.
It's suitable for this. Hahaha , you
finally went into the water
to show everyone the underwater world of Oman.
After searching underwater for about half an hour,
we only found some relatively small naked-breasted eels
Yououpi.
We saw an octopus and we caught it.
Can we use octopus as bait
to catch eels?
Can we use octopus to catch eels? Yes,
okay
.
Ok, brother, he is really fierce
in fighting octopus underwater.
We plan to use octopus to catch naked eel.
I don’t know if it will be
too successful. I can’t bite
the knife anymore. My knife
is so big. Yooupi
hasn’t picked up
the octopus
yet . You can use this to
catch eels
. It’s OK. It’s
because the habit of naked eels
is to live in underwater coral colonies.
We need to constantly dive 5 to 6 meters to find
this operation. This is the first time I am
very excited
about the Yooupi
octopus. It won't eat
the fish. Let's try it.
Then I will change the fish
Yooupi and use the lobster as bait for
you. It’s too luxurious.
I haven’t caught any fish.
There are so many lobsters in Oman.
I feel like there are lobsters everywhere under the water.
I use lobsters to catch naked-breasted eels.
I’d like to ask if it’s luxurious.
Because there are waves today
, the underwater visibility is not very high.
We need to spend more. We spent a lot of time
searching for the giant naked eel underwater.
After searching more than 20 caves on the seabed, we
finally found it.
At that moment
, Brother OK and I were so happy
that we thought it was no accident that the air force would
find this naked eel.
It's like an underwater monster in the cave
. Its size and pattern are very bluffing.
Yooupi,
you shoot, or should I shoot
together. Shoot
together. Ok, Ok. It
's too big.
Yooupi, pull it faster
, don't let it run into the cave, hurry
up. Be careful, it bites you.
Don’t pull it too close. Yooupi
Ok
Photographer: Did you hit it?
Did you hit it?
It’s so big.
Let
me
show you. This giant monster
is so big
. I’m so scared. It took
two shots to hit
me and me. Brother fired one shot.
Brother's shot hit it directly on the spine,
so it didn't curl up.
When I hit it just now, I was very excited.
I wanted to get it
. Then brother kept reminding me not to scratch it.
If it bites you, you will Roll up your whole piece of meat.
Roll out your whole piece of meat.
Yooupi
, I told you that I would take you to make a conger eel with thick thighs
to see if your
thighs are thick. My brother said it is thicker than my thighs.
It is really thicker than my thighs.
And it’s so big and long.
It looks even better when it’s in a hole under the water.
With its head sticking out in the space, it
feels very shocking.
And the patterns on its body
look like that of a snake. Brother,
did you cook it well at the barbecue last time?
This thing is
not very tasty.
Today I will cook you a
Sichuan braised eel.
Is it
really
okay? Let’s go.
Hahaha
, it made my face full of sand.
Old guys, look at this eel.
Now I will just cook it and stew it
in the evening. I have a braised eel for me to eat
. The skin is so
fat that it
’s hard to cut it. I feel like I
cut it into sections and I can’t even pierce
it. The skin is as thick as a rubber band.
I’ll burn this piece today for me to eat
. I cut it into sections and froze it.
It was too big to eat.
I blanched the eel and boiled the water.
Now I started to
simmer the eel until it was fat. Then I fried some potatoes
and chili and put it here
. I stewed
the eel with the potatoes
and simmered it till
it gets fragrant. S I won’t
tell you who it is. When the pot
is stewed, it
turns red.
I'm asking you to
see if it smells good through the screen.
I can't help it.
I can only eat it. You can only watch it.
Sprinkle a little chopped green onion at the end.
Brother Perfect comes to eat it.
You can already smell the aroma.
Look at me. I made this
Sichuan version of grilled eel for you
. Just look at how it looks and you will win
. You have to take a bite of
Yooupi. I ate it first. I
thought this piece was good
and fat.
I didn’t get this delicious last time at BBQ
. This is for sure.
The taste has gone in.
It’s so good.
It’s so good. It
’s so satisfying.
You can’t even take one bite.
I’m telling you, I
usually do this in a small way. But here
Aman still has to find my OK brother to spend some time
with Yooupi like this.
I'm going to Mauritius. I
heard that the goods there are bigger.
If you have time, come to me
and we can work on bigger goods together.
You go and scout first and I'll be there later.